   { 
  "status": 200,
  "status_message": "Success",
  "response":
   [ 
    {
       "userId" : "11",
      "categoryId" :  "FILMS",
        "question" : "Which car manufacturer was the first to win 100 F1 races?",
        "option1" : "Ferrari",
        "option2" : "Nissan",
        "option3" : "Ford",
        "option4" : "",
        "correct" : "Ferrari."
      "total": "1"
    },
    {
       "userId" : "12",
      "categoryId" :  "MUSIC",
       
        "question" : "In the professional era which woman has won the most titles at Wimbledon [singles, doubles and mixed] ?",
        "option1" : "Venus",
        "option2" : "Hingis",
        "option3" : "Martina Navratilova",
        "option4" : "Waynetta",
        "correct" : "Martina Navratilova"
      "total": "1"
    },
      {
      
       "userId" : "27",
      "categoryId" :  "ANIMALS",
        "question" : "How many times have Liverpool been relegated from the top flight of English football?",
        "option1" : "Four",
        "option2" : "Three",
        "option3" : "Two",
        "option4" : "Five",
        "correct" : "Three"
      "total": "1"
    },
  
    {
      
       "userId" : "24",
      "categoryId" :  "POLITICS",
        "question" : "How many times have Liverpool been relegated from the top flight of English football?",
        "option1" : "Four",
        "option2" : "Three",
        "option3" : "Two",
        "option4" : "Five",
        "correct" : "Three"
      "total": "1"
    },
     {
       "userId" : "31",
      "categoryId" :  "ANIME",
        "question" : "Which car manufacturer was the first to win 100 F1 races?",
        "option1" : "Ferrari",
        "option2" : "Nissan",
        "option3" : "Ford",
        "option4" : "",
        "correct" : "Ferrari."
      "total": "1"
    },
    {
       "userId" : "25",
      "categoryId" :  "ART",
       
        "question" : "In the professional era which woman has won the most titles at Wimbledon [singles, doubles and mixed] ?",
        "option1" : "Venus",
        "option2" : "Hingis",
        "option3" : "Martina Navratilova",
        "option4" : "Waynetta",
        "correct" : "Martina Navratilova"
      "total": "1"
    },
 
     {
       "userId" : "21",
      "categoryId" :  "SPORTS",
        "question" : "Which car manufacturer was the first to win 100 F1 races?",
        "option1" : "Ferrari",
        "option2" : "Nissan",
        "option3" : "Ford",
        "option4" : "",
        "correct" : "Ferrari."
      "total": "1"
    },
    {
       "userId" : "9",
      "categoryId" :  " GENERAL",
       
        "question" : "In the professional era which woman has won the most titles at Wimbledon [singles, doubles and mixed] ?",
        "option1" : "Venus",
        "option2" : "Hingis",
        "option3" : "Martina Navratilova",
        "option4" : "Waynetta",
        "correct" : "Martina Navratilova"
      "total": "1"
    },
     {
       "userId" : "18",
      "categoryId" :  "COMPUTER",
        "question" : "Which car manufacturer was the first to win 100 F1 races?",
        "option1" : "Ferrari",
        "option2" : "Nissan",
        "option3" : "Ford",
        "option4" : "",
        "correct" : "Ferrari."
      "total": "1"
    },
    {
       "userId" : "19",
      "categoryId" :  "MATHEMATICS",
       
        "question" : "In the professional era which woman has won the most titles at Wimbledon [singles, doubles and mixed] ?",
        "option1" : "Venus",
        "option2" : "Hingis",
        "option3" : "Martina Navratilova",
        "option4" : "Waynetta",
        "correct" : "Martina Navratilova"
      "total": "1"
    },
     {
       "userId" : "15",
      "categoryId" :  " GAMES",
        "question" : "Which car manufacturer was the first to win 100 F1 races?",
        "option1" : "Ferrari",
        "option2" : "Nissan",
        "option3" : "Ford",
        "option4" : "",
        "correct" : "Ferrari."
      "total": "1"
    },
    {
       "userId" : "14",
      "categoryId" :  " TELEVISION",
       
        "question" : "In the professional era which woman has won the most titles at Wimbledon [singles, doubles and mixed] ?",
        "option1" : "Venus",
        "option2" : "Hingis",
        "option3" : "Martina Navratilova",
        "option4" : "Waynetta",
        "correct" : "Martina Navratilova"
      "total": "1"
    }
   ]} 
    
   
    
